<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nixon Enraght-Moony</title>
    <link>https://adotinthevoid.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nixon Enraght-Moony</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adotinthevoid.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://adotinthevoid.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adotinthevoid.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Inigo Montoya. I have the following qualities:
 I rock a great mustache I&amp;rsquo;m extremely loyal to my family  What else do you need?
my history To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m having some trouble remembering right now, so why don&amp;rsquo;t you just watch my movie and it will answer all your questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://adotinthevoid.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adotinthevoid.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Please hire me</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta</title>
      <link>https://adotinthevoid.github.io/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adotinthevoid.github.io/meta/</guid>
      <description>Colophon Site generated by Hugo, which is great. Unfortunately, Github pages doesn&amp;rsquo;t grok it, so we have 3 repositories
 The site itself: Contains the content The theme: Contains the theme (see below) The github pages: Contains the generated files  Theme  Theme is hyde by @mdo. Ported to hugo by spf13. Additional Modifications by me.  You can learn more about the theme here
Syntax highting Syntax Highlighting is done via chroma on server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme</title>
      <link>https://adotinthevoid.github.io/theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adotinthevoid.github.io/theme/</guid>
      <description>This site runs a modified version of spf13’s hugo port of @mdo&amp;lsquo;s hyde theme for jekyll
Modifications made:
 Use \(\KaTeX\) Better date format (Mon, Jan 2, 2006 to January 2, 2006) Have a blog and non blog section  Blog sections have dates, non-blog doesn&amp;rsquo;t Blog uses short list, non-blog doesn&amp;rsquo;t Home page has content, not blog list   No home link in sidebar: The site name above does that Improved Copyright handling: Allow customization of copyright text Add table of contents option Add not_a_list type: This is a list type where the list is actualy a single.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>